Guide to the Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection, 1990-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Tapes, 1990-1996
  - Tape 226
    - Total Body Power. Lifetime. 1995 Sept. 18. 2:30 AM.
    - Chroma Trim Gum. WNBC-TV. 1995 Sept. 9. 5:30 AM.
    - QRB Ultimate Cleaner. WABC. 1995 Aug. 27. 6:00 AM.
  - Tape 227
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1995 Sept. 16. 7:30 AM.
    - Metrinch tools. CNBC. 1995 Sept. 10. 3:00 AM.
    - MGM/UA Home Movies. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 7. 11:30 AM.
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 14. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 228
    - Hydron Skin Care. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 21. 8:30 AM.
    - Fast Track Exerciser. WNYW-TV. 1995 Oct. 29. 9:30 AM.
    - United Home Karaoke. WNBC-TV. 1995 Oct. 28. 4:00 AM.
    - Quicksilver Cleaning. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 28. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 229
    - EZ Krunch Exerciser. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 28. 11:00 AM.
    - Bee Alive Royal Jelly. KWHB. 1995 Oct. 18. 1:30 PM.
    - Power Walk Plus. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 4. 9:00 AM.
    - Total Body Comfort. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 4. 10:00 AM.
  - Tape 230
    - Contemporary Collectibles. Lifetime. 1995 Oct. 8. 7:00 AM.
    - Oxford Health Plans. WCBS. 1995 Oct. 14. 2:30 PM.
    - Troy-Bilt Chipper. WABC. 1995 Oct. 14. 5:30 AM.
    - Wonder Cooker. WABC. 1995 Oct. 15. 6:00 AM.
  - Tape 231
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 25. 7:30 AM.
    - Oxford Health Plans. WCBS. 1995 Oct. 14. 2:30 PM.
    - Sega Pico Interactive. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 11. 11:00 AM.
    - Lean Mean Fat Reducing. WNBC-TV. 1995 Dec. 11. 2:38 AM.
  - Tape 232
    - Ab Roller Plus. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 11. 7:00 AM.
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 11. 7:30 AM.
    - Bowdazzler. WCBS. 1995 Nov. 12. 3:00 PM.
    - Perfect Equation. WWOR-TV. 1995 Nov. 18. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 233
    - Mega System. WWOR-TV. 1995 Dec. 2. 10:30 AM.
    - Years Away Beauty Lifts. WNBC-TV. 1995 May 13. 4:30 AM.
    - Electronic Cop Security. WABC. 1995 Dec. 3. 6:00 AM.
    - 1-800-Flowers Florists. ABC. 1995 Dec. 8. 6:00 AM.
  - Tape 234
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1995 Dec. 9. 7:30 AM.
    - Sony Instant Surround Sound System. WWOR-TV. 1995 Dec. 9. 11:30 AM.
    - Food Dehydrator. WNYW-TV. 1995 Dec. 17. 9:30 AM.
    - Magnavox Home Security. Comedy Central. 1995 Nov. 19. 5:00 AM.
  - Tape 335
    - Ab Trainer. Sci-Fi. 1995 Dec. 31. 8:30 AM.
    - Health Rider. WWOR-TV. 1995 Dec. 30. 8:00 AM.
    - Hydron Skin Care. WWOR-TV. 1995 Oct. 21. 8:30 AM.
    - Cardioglide. WNBC-TV. 1994 Nov. 15. 3:06 AM.
  - Tape 336
    - Diabetes Watch. KPIX. 1995 July 22. 6:30 PM.
    - Century 21 Real Estate. WJW. 1995 Nov. 19. 10:09 AM.
    - Elek-Tek Computer Store. HCNB. 1995 Nov. 18. 11:00 AM.
    - For Women Only. WTTE. 1996 Jan. 22. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 337
    - Poetic Return of Pablo Neruda. WNYW-TV. 1996 Jan. 7. 9:30 AM.
    - Joe Montana's Contour Cross. WWOR-TV. 1996 Jan. 6. 10:30 AM.
    - Mon Amie Cosmetics. WWOR-TV. 1996 Jan. 13. 6:39 PM.
    - American Home Business. NBC. 1996 Jan. 10. 3:06 AM.
  - Tape 338
    - New Media Calling. WWOR-TV. 1996 Jan. 27. 1:30 AM.
    - Don Lapre Making Money Package. ETV. 1996 Feb. 9. 4:00 AM.
    - Golden Opportunity Jewelry. Family Channel. 1996 Feb. 8. 4:00 AM.
    - Universal Seminars. NBC. 1996 Jan. 12. 2:37 AM.
  - Tape 339
    - Assist. CNN. 1996 Jan. 25. 11:58 PM.
    - Looney Tunes. Lifetime. 1996 Jan. 24. 1:11 PM.
    - Years Away Beauty Lifts. WNBC-TV. 1996 Feb. 8. 2:38 AM.
  - Tape 340
    - Cholestaway Dietary Supplement. WWOR-TV. 1996. No time.
    - Financial Concepts. WNYW-TV. 1996. No time.
    - The Book of Mormon. AT. 1996. No time.
    - Aroma-Trim. CNBC. 1996. No time.
  - Tape 341
    - Carleton Sheets. CNBC. 1996 Feb. 13. 3:00 AM.
    - Waltham Formula Canned and Dry Dog Food. WNBC-TV. 1996 Feb. 13. 3:06 AM.
    - Mon Amie Cosmetics. CNBC. 1996 Feb. 12. 4:30 AM.
    - Years Away Beauty Lifts. WNBC-TV. 1996 Feb. 8. 2:38 AM.
  - Tape 342
    - Black Magic Spray N Wax. TNN. 1996 Mar. 10. 4:30 AM.
    - Water Processor. WTBS. 1996 Feb. 19. 3:30 AM.
    - Secrets to Making Money. Comedy Central. 1996 Feb. 15. 4:00 AM.
    - Money Makers Live Program. Comedy Central. 1996 Feb. 15. 4:30 AM.
  - Tape 343
    - Prolong Super Lubricants. Speed Channel. 1996 Mar. 16. 7:30 AM.
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1996 Mar. 16. 7:30 AM.
    - Denise Austin's Complete Workout. WWOR-TV. 1996 Mar. 9. 7:30 AM.
    - Motor Up Additive. TNN. 1996 Mar. 16. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 344
    - Health Rider. WWOR-TV. 1995 Dec. 30. 8:00 AM.
    - Chiropractic Centennial. WWOR-TV. 1996 Mar. 2. 10:00 AM.
    - Universal Seminars. NBC. 1996 Jan. 12. 2:37 AM.
  - Tape 345
    - Success and You. WNBC-TV. 1996 Apr. 1. 2:37 AM.
    - Secrets to Making Money. Sci-Fi. 1996 Mar. 24. 8:31 AM.
    - Lubricator 2000 Super. WWOR-TV. 1996 Apr. 6. 8:00 AM.
    - Ruth Prodan's Burner. CNBC. 1996 Apr. 1. 3:30 AM.
  - Tape 346
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1996 Apr. 27. 7:30 AM.
    - Pilates Performer. Lifetime. 1996 Apr. 26. 7:00 AM.
    - Computer Personalities. TNN. 1996 May 4. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 347
    - Nutrivida Vitamins. WNJU. 1996 June 1. 2:30 PM.
    - Hoover Dirt Finder Vacuum. WDIV. 1996 May 25. 4:30 PM.
    - Aroma-Trim. WTTV. 1996 Mar. 22. 9:31 AM.
    - Cardio Walk Exerciser. WCIU. 1996 Feb. 10. 9:00 AM.
  - Tape 348
    - Zoom Personal Styling Salon. Lifetime. 1996 May 13. 7:00 AM.
    - Nobody Beats the Wiz. MSG. 1996 May 15. 8:42 AM.
    - Smart Walk Triple Action Treadmill. Discovery. 1996 May 16. 5:00 AM.
    - Team Jenner Winning Formula. WWOR-TV. 1996 May 18. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 349 (Box 9)
    - Perfect Abs. WWOR-TV. 1996 May 19. 7:00 AM.
    - Team Jenner Winning Formula. WWOR-TV. 1996 May 18. 7:00 AM.
    - Secrets of Success. WWOR-TV. 1996 May 20. 7:30 AM.
    - New Jersey Education Association. WWOR-TV. 1996 May 25. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 350
    - Power Wash. WWOR-TV. 1996 May 25. 9:30 AM.
    - Hidden Keys to Loving Relationships. Lifetime. 1996 May 28. 7:00 AM.
    - Larouche for President. WNYW-TV. 1996 June 2. 9:30 AM.
    - Time Life Recording. Lifetime. 1996 June 12. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 352
    - Magikan Trashcan. WWOR-TV. 1996. No time.
    - Sweet Simplicity. Lifetime. 1996. No time.
    - Bee Alive Royal Jelly. WWOR-TV. 1996. No time.
    - Smooth & Natural Facial. WWOR-TV. 1996. No time.
  - Tape 353
    - Barbie My Fair Lady Collection. Lifetime. 1996No time.
    - Co-Eds. WWOR-TV. 1996No time.
    - Ever Last. CBS. 1996No time.
    - Ab Shaper. WWOR-TV. 1996No time.
  - Tape 354
    - Tony Little's Abs. WWOR-TV. 1996 Aug. 8. 8:30 AM.
    - World Business. WWOR-TV. 1996 Aug. 10. 7:00 AM.
    - MGM/UA Presents Pee-Wee. WWOR-TV. 1996 Aug. 10. 8:30 AM.